<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- Copyright 2018–2021 elementary, Inc. <contact@elementary.io> -->
<component type="desktop">
  <id>io.elementary.code</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_group>elementary</project_group>
  <project_license>GPL-3.0+</project_license>
  <name>Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_TW">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh_CN">代码</name>
  <name xml:lang="uz">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Код</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kod</name>
  <name xml:lang="szl">Kod</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kod</name>
  <name xml:lang="sr">Код</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Koda</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kód</name>
  <name xml:lang="si">කේතය</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Код</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kod</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਕੋਡ</name>
  <name xml:lang="oc">Còdi</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="nb">Kode</name>
  <name xml:lang="ms">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="mr">कोड</name>
  <name xml:lang="lt">Kodas</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">코드</name>
  <name xml:lang="ja">コード</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Codice</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="hu">Kód</name>
  <name xml:lang="hi">कोड</name>
  <name xml:lang="he">קוד</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr_CA">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Koodi</name>
  <name xml:lang="fa">کد</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="eo">Kodo</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_GB">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_CA">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="en_AU">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Κώδικας</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="ckb">كۆد</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Codi</name>
  <name xml:lang="bs">Kod</name>
  <name xml:lang="bo">Code</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كود</name>
  <summary>The editor that works for you</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh_CN">适合您的编辑器</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор, який працює для вас</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sizin için çalışan metin editörü</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Editor, ktorý pracuje pre vás</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Редактор, который работает для Вас</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">O editor que funciona para si</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor, który działa dla ciebie</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">De tekstverwerker die het werk voor jou doet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ja">便利なエディター</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="hu">A megfelelő szerkesztő ön számára</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="he">עורך הטקסט שעובד בשבילך</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">L'éditeur qui travaille pour vous</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">El editor que trabaja para ti</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en_GB">The editor that works for you</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Der Editor, der für Sie arbeitet</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Editor, který pracuje pro vás</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ckb">ئەو دەستکاریکەرەی کە بۆ تۆ کار دەکات</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">L'editor que us funciona</summary>
  <description>
    <p>Whether you're writing in Markdown or managing a complex app codebase, Code is the lightweight but full-featured editor for you. It auto-saves your files to ensure they're always up-to-date, and it remembers your tabs so you never lose your spot—even between sessions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">无论您是使用 Markdown 编写还是管理复杂的应用程序代码库，Code 都是适合您的轻量级但功能齐全的编辑器。 它会自动保存您的文件以确保它们始终是最新的，并且它会记住您的选项卡，因此您永远不会丢失您的位置 - 即使在会话之间也是如此。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Незалежно від того, чи пишете ви в Markdown або керуєте складною кодовою базою застосунків, Код — це легкий, але повнофункціональний редактор для вас. Він автоматично зберігає ваші файли, щоб вони завжди були актуальними й запам'ятовує ваші вкладки, щоб ви ніколи не втратите місце, на якому зупинилися, навіть в перервах між сеансами.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">İster Markdown formatında yazıyor, ister karmaşık bir uygulama kod tabanını yönetiyor olun, Kod sizin için hafif ama tam özellikli bir düzenleyicidir. Her zaman güncel olduklarından emin olmak için dosyalarınızı otomatik olarak kaydeder ve sekmelerinizi hatırlar, böylece oturumlar arasında bile yerinizi asla kaybetmezsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Či už píšete v Markdown alebo spravujete komplexnú aplikačnú databázu, Kód je nenáročný, ale plne funkčný editor pre vás. Automaticky ukladá vaše súbory, aby boli vždy aktuálne. Pamätá si tiež otvorené karty, aby ste sa nikdy nestratili, dokonca ani pri prepínaní niekoľkých relácií.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Пишете ли вы используя Markdown или редактируете код сложного проекта, Код — это лёгкий, но полнофункциональный редактор для Вас. Он автоматически сохраняет ваши файлы, а также запоминает открытые вкладки. Вы никогда не потеряете место, на котором остановились, даже в перерывах между сессиями.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Nieważne czy piszesz dokument w Markdownie czy zarządzasz skomplikowanym kodem aplikacji, Kod jest lekkim, lecz w pełni funkcjonalnym edytorem dla Ciebie. Automatycznie zapisuje Twoje pliki by zapewnić, że zawsze są aktualne, oraz zapamiętuje Twoje zakładki, więc nigdy nie tracisz miejsca, w którym skończyłeś – nawet pomiędzy sesjami.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Of je nou in Markdown schrijft of een complexe codebase beheert, Code is een lichtgewicht maar volwaardige editor. Het slaat automatische je bestanden op zodat je altijd up-to-date bent, en het herinnert je tabbladen zodat je nooit je plaats verliest—zelfs tussen sessies in.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">Markdown で文書を作成するときも、複雑なアプリのソースコードを管理するときも、軽量ながら高機能な“コード”はぴったりです。ファイルを自動保存して、常に最新の状態を維持します。また、タブを保存し次回起動時に復元するので、時間が経っても最後に編集した箇所を見失うことはありません。</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Akár Markdown-fájlokat szerkeszt, akár összetett kódbázist kezel, a Kód a megfelelő szerkesztő az ön számára. Automatikusan menti a fájlokat, hogy mindig aktuálisak legyenek, illetve megjegyzi a megnyitott lapokat — még munkamenetek közt is — így ön mindig tudni fogja, hol tart a munkájában.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">בין אם בכתיבת Markdown או בניהול מאגר קוד מורכב של יישום, קוד הוא עורך קליל אך עשיר ביכולות עבורך. הוא שומר את הקבצים שלך אוטומטית כדי לוודא שהם תמיד עדכניים והוא זוכר את הלשוניות שלך כדי לאפשר חזרה מאיפה שהפסקת, אפילו לאחר הפוגה ממושכת.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Que vous écriviez en Markdown ou que vous gériez le code d'une application complexe, Code est l'éditeur léger mais complet qu'il vous faut. Il enregistre automatiquement vos fichiers pour qu'ils soient toujours à jour et mémorise vos onglets pour que vous ne vous perdiez jamais, même entre deux sessions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Ya sea que esté escribiendo en Markdown o administrando una código de una aplicación compleja, Code es el editor liviano pero con todas las funciones para usted. Guarda automáticamente sus archivos para asegurarse de que estén siempre actualizados y recuerda sus pestañas para que nunca pierda su trabajo incluso entre sesiones.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Whether you're writing in Markdown or managing a complex app codebase, Code is the lightweight but full-featured editor for you. It auto-saves your files to ensure they're always up-to-date, and it remembers your tabs so you never lose your spot—even between sessions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Ob Sie in Markdown schreiben oder eine komplexe Anwednungs-Codebasis managen - Code ist der schlanke und dennoch funktionsreiche Editor für Sie. Er speichert Ihre Dateien ganz automatisch, so dass diese immer auf dem aktuellen Stand sind. Außerdem merkt sich Code, welche Tabs Sie geöffnet hatten, sodass Sie nie den Faden verlieren. Sogar über mehrere Sitzungen hinweg.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Automaticky ukládá soubory, aby byli vždy aktuální. Pamatuji si také otevřené panely, abyste se už nikdy neztratili, ani při přepínání několika sezení. Automaticky ukládá soubory, aby bylo zajištěno, že jsou aktuální a pamatuje si otevřené panely, takže nikdy neztratíte své soustředění – ani mezi relacemi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">تۆ ئەم ئەپە بۆ نووسینێکی سادە بەکار بهێنیت یان پڕۆگرامینگی پڕۆژەیەکی گەورەی پێ بکەیت، ئەوا هیچ کێشەت بۆ دروست نابێت. کۆد ئەپێکی زۆر سادە و سوکەڵەیە بەڵام پڕە لە تایبتەمەندی. خۆکارە پەڕگەکانت پاشەکەوت دەکات ( Auto-save) و تابەکان لە یاد نەکات کە کردبووتنەوە، تەنانەت ئەگەر سێشنیش کۆتایی پێ بهێنیت.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Tant si escriviu a Markdown com si gestioneu una base de codis d’aplicacions complexa, el Code és l’editor lleuger però amb totes les funcions. Desa automàticament els fitxers per assegurar-se que estiguin sempre actualitzats i recorda les pestanyes perquè mai no perdeu el punt, fins i tot entre sessions.</p>
    <p>Designed around a project-based workflow, Code knows about your separate codebases. It comes with helpful Git integration to create and switch between branches and show changed files and lines within your projects.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">围绕基于项目的工作流程设计，Code 了解您单独的代码库。 它带有有用的 Git 集成，可以在分支之间创建和切换，并在项目中显示更改的文件和行。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Розроблений для роботи з різними проєктами, Код знає про ваші окремі кодові бази. Він поставляється з інтеграцією Git для створення та перемикання між гілками та показу змінених файлів та рядків у ваших проєктах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Proje tabanlı bir iş akışı için tasarlanan Kode, ayrı kod tabanlarınızı bilir. Dallar oluşturma, bunlar arasında geçiş yapmak ve projelerinizdeki değişen dosya ve satırları göstermek için yararlı Git entegrasyonuyla birlikte gelir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Navrhnutý okolo projektového spôsobu práce, Kód vie o vašich oddelených zdrojových kódoch. Prichádza s nápomocným napojením na Git pre vytváranie a prepínanie medzi vetvami a zobrazovanie zmien v súboroch a riadkoch v rámci vašich projektov.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Разработан для работы с различными проектами, Код знает о ваших отдельных кодовых базах. Он поставляется с интеграцией Git для создания и переключения между ветками, а также для отображения измененных файлов и строк в ваших проектах.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Zaprojektowany z myślą o pracy z projektami, Kod wie o twoich osobnych repozytoriach kodu. Jest wyposażony w pomocną integrację z Gitem, by tworzyć i zmieniać branch'e oraz pokazywać zmienione pliki i linie kodu w twoich projektach.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ontworpen rondom een project gebaseerde workflow, Code is bekkend met je verschillende codebases. Het komt met behulpzame Git-integratie om Git-takken aan te maken, te schakelen tussen takken en om veranderingen in bestanden en individuele lijnen te tonen binnen u projecten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">“コード”はプロジェクト単位のワークフロー向けにデザインされているので、コードベースごとに認識されるようになっています。便利な Git との統合機能が搭載されており、ブランチを作成したり変更したり、プロジェクト内のファイルや行の差分を表示したりできます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">תוכנן סביב תהליכי עבודה מבוססי מיזמים, Code יודע על מאגרי הקוד הנפרדים שלך. בכלי יש יכולות שילוב מול Git כדי ליצור ולהחליף בין ענפים ולהציג קבצים ושורות שהשתנו בתוך המיזמים שלך.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Conçu pour fonctionner par projet, Code reconnaît vos bases de code distinctes. Il est livré avec une intégration Git utile pour créer et passer d'une branche à l'autre et afficher les fichiers et lignes modifiés dans vos projets.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Diseñado en torno a un flujo de trabajo basado en proyectos, Code conoce tus código de forma independiente. Viene con una útil integración de Git para crear y cambiar entre ramas y mostrar archivos y líneas modificados dentro de sus proyectos.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Designed around a project-based workflow, Code knows about your separate codebases. It comes with helpful Git integration to create and switch between branches and show changed files and lines within your projects.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Da er um einen projektbasierten Workflow herum designt ist, weiß Code um Ihre separierten Codebases. Er beinhaltet hilfreiche Git-Integration um Branches zu erstellen und zwischen ihnen zu wechseln. Er zeigt ausserdem geänderte Dateien und Zeilen innerhalb ihrer Projekte an.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Navrženo kolem projektového způsobu práce, Code ví o oddělených zdrojových kódech. Přichází s nápomocným napojením na Git pro vytváření a přepínání mezi větvemi a zobrazuje změněné soubory a řádky v rámci projektů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">کۆد، لەسەر بنەمای پڕۆژە دیزاین کراوە. ئەم ئەپە دەزانێت کە دەکرێت تۆ بنکەکۆدی جیاوازت هەبن. یەکێکی تر لە تایبەتمەندییەکانی بریتییە لە گیت بۆ دروستکردنی و هاتووچۆکردن لە نێوان بڕانچەکاندا، هەروەها دێر و پەڕگە دەستکاریکراوەکانت لەناو پڕۆژەکەتدا پشان دەدات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Dissenyat al voltant d’un flux de treball basat en projectes, el Code coneix les vostres bases de codis separades. Inclou una integració útil amb Git per crear i canviar entre branques i mostrar fitxers i línies canviats als projectes.</p>
    <p>Work with your language: whether you're crafting code in Vala, scripting with PHP, or marking things up in HTML, Code has you covered. Experience full syntax highlighting with nearly all programming, scripting, and markup languages.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">海纳百川！无论您是 Vala 老手、PHP 专家还是 HTML 大师，Code 都能满足您的需求。语法高亮功能支持几乎所有编程语言、脚本语言和标记语言。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Працюйте зі своєю мовою: чи пишете ви код на Vala, чи скрипти на PHP або робите щось з HTML, Код прикриє вас. Підсвічування синтаксису багатьох мов програмування, скриптів і розмітки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kendi dilinizle çalışın: ister Vala ile kodluyor olun, ister PHP ile script yazıyor veya HTML dosyası düzenliyor olun, Kod her zaman yanınızda. Tam sözdizimi vurgulaması ile neredeyse bütün programlama dilleri ile uyumun tecrübesini yaşayın.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Pracujte s vaším jazykom: či už zostrojujete kód vo Vale, skriptujete s PHP alebo pracujete v HTML, Kód je tu pre vás. Určite oceníte úplné zvýrazňovanie syntaxe s takmer všetkými programovacími, skriptovacími a značkovacími jazykmi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Работайте со своим языком: создаете ли вы код на Vala, пишите скрипты на PHP или делаете разметку на HTML, Код поможет вам. Вы можете воспользоваться полной подсветкой синтаксиса почти во всех языках программирования, скриптов и разметки.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Działa w Twoim języku, niezależnie czy piszesz kod w Vala, skrypt PHP, czy markery w HTML-u, Kod Ci w tym pomoże. Doświadcz pełnego kolorowania składni w prawie wszystkich językach programowania, skryptowych i markupowych.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Werkt met uw taal: Of u nu in Vala code schrijft, een script maakt in PHP of opmaak bouwt in HTML, Code is er voor u. Benut volledige syntax-markering met bijna alle programmeer-, script-, en markuptalen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">あの言語にも、この言語にも、対応。Vala でコーディングしていても、PHP でスクリプティングしていても、HTML でマークアップしていても、“コード”はあなたをサポートします。完璧なシンタックスハイライトが、ほぼすべてのプログラミング言語・スクリプティング言語・マークアップ言語で利用可能です。</p>
    <p xml:lang="hu">Dolgozzon a kedvenc nyelvén: akár Vala kódolással, PHP szkripteléssel vagy HTML szerkesztéssel foglalkozik, a Kód alkalmas a feladatra. Tapasztalja meg a teljes szintaxiskiemelést szinte minden programozási, szkript- és jelölőnyelven.</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">עובד בשפה שלך: בין אם בחרישת קוד ב־Vala, כתיבת סקריפטים עם PHP או תיוג דברים ב־HTML, קוד מגבה אותך. ניתן להתנסות בהדגשת תחביר מלאה כמעט בכל שפות התכנות, הסקריפטים והתגיות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Il fonctionne avec votre langage. Que vous élaboriez du code en Vala, des scripts PHP, ou des pages HTML, Code est là pour vous. Profitez d’une coloration syntaxique complète avec presque tous les langages de programmation, des scripts ou de balisage.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Trabaje con su lenguaje: ya sea creando código en Vala, creando scripts con PHP o maquetando en HTML, Code lo tiene todo cubierto. Experimenta el resaltado de sintaxis completo con casi todos los lenguajes de programación, secuencias de comandos y marcas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Work with your language: whether you're crafting code in Vala, scripting with PHP, or marking things up in HTML, Code has you covered. Experience full syntax highlighting with nearly all programming, scripting, and markup languages.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Arbeiten Sie mit der Programmiersprache Ihrer Wahl: Ob Sie in Vala programmieren, PHP-Code schreiben oder Text in HTML verfassen – Code deckt all Ihre Anforderungen ab. Erleben Sie, wie Code in fast allen Programmier-, Skript- und Markup-Sprachen die perfekte Syntax-Hervorhebung beherrscht.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Umí pracovat s vaším jazykem: ať už vytváříte kód ve Vale, skriptujete v PHP, nebo značkujete pomocí HTML, Code je tu pro vás. Jistě oceníte plné zvýrazňování syntaxe s téměř všemi programovacími, skriptovacími a značkovacími jazyky.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">بەو زمانە بنووسە کە خۆت دەتەوێت: گرنگ نییە کە تۆ کار بە ڤالا بکەیت، یان خەریکی نووسینی سکریپت بیت بە PHP یان پێشەوەی وێبێک دابڕێژیت بە HTML، کۆد خەمی لێت خواردووە، بەنزیکەیی پاڵپشتی سینتاکسی تەواوی زمانەکانی بەرنامەنووسین، سکریپکردن و مارکەپ کردن دەکات و یەرمەتی هایلایتینگ دەدات.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Funciona amb la vostre llenguatge. Tant si elaboreu codi en Vala, feu scripts amb PHP o marqueu coses en HTML, el Codi us té cobert. Experimenteu el realçament complet de sintaxi amb gairebé tota la programació, seqüències d'ordres i llenguatges de marcatge.</p>
    <p>Find anything in your current file, specific folders, or your whole project with options for case-sensitivity and regular expressions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">使用区分大小写和正则表达式的选项，在当前文件、特定文件夹或整个项目中查找任何内容。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Пошук у поточному файлі, конкретних теках або у всьому проєкті будь-чого з параметрами регістрозалежності та регулярних виразів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Büyük/küçük harf duyarlılığı ve normal ifadeler arama seçenekleriyle mevcut dosyanızda, belirli klasörlerde veya tüm projenizdeki herhangi bir şeyi bulun.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Nájdite čokoľvek v práve otvorenom súbore, v konkrétnych priečinkoch alebo v celom projekte s možnosťami pre rozlišovanie medzi malými a veľkými písmenami a bežnými výrazmi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Находите всё что угодно в текущем файле, определённых папках, или целом проекте с опцией выбора регистра и регулярных выражений.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Znajdź cokolwiek w aktualnym pliku, konkretnych folderach lub w całym twoim projekcie z opcjami rozróżnienia małych i wielkich liter oraz wyrażeniami regularnymi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Vind alles in u huidige bestand, specifieke folders, of u hele project met opties voor hoofdlettergevoeligheid en reguliere uitdrukkingen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">表示中のファイルや特定のフォルダー、プロジェクト全体を対象に自由自在に検索できます。大文字・小文字の区別や正規表現を使った検索も可能です。</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">ניתן למצוא כל דבר, בין אם בקובץ הנוכחי, בתיקיות מסוימות או בכל המיזם שלך אם אפשרויות לרגישות רישיות וביטויים רגולריים.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Trouvez n'importe quoi dans votre fichier actuel, dans des dossiers spécifiques ou dans l'ensemble de votre projet grâce aux options de sensibilité à la casse et aux expressions régulières.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Encuentra cualquier cosa en tu archivo actual, carpetas específicas o todo tu proyecto con opciones para la distinción entre mayúsculas y minúsculas y expresiones regulares.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Find anything in your current file, specific folders, or your whole project with options for case-sensitivity and regular expressions.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Finden Sie alles in Ihrer aktuellen Datei, Ordnern oder Ihrem ganzen Projekt mit Optionen für Groß/Kleinschreibung und reguläre Ausdrücke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Najděte cokoli v právě otevřeném souboru, konkrétních složkách nebo v celém projektu pomocí voleb pro (ne)rozlišování mezi malými/VELKÝMI písmeny a regulárních výrazů.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">بۆ هەر چییەک دەگەڕێت بگەڕێ لەناو پەڕگە کراوەکەی ئێستاتدا، یان لە ناو تەواوی پڕۆژەکەتدا بە بەکارهێنانی بژاردەکانی هەستیارەکەیس (case-sensitivity) و دەستەواژە باوەکان.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Cerqueu qualsevol cosa al fitxer actual, a carpetes específiques o a tot el projecte amb les opcions per distingir entre majúscules i minúscules i expressions regulars.</p>
    <p>Smart features throughout: automatic indentation, smart cut/copy behavior, visible whitespace for selected text and at the end of lines by default, and optional extensions for Markdown actions, spell checking, whitespace trimming, word completion, and more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">智能功能贯穿始终：自动缩进、智能剪切/复制行为、默认情况下所选文本和行尾的可见空白，以及 Markdown 操作的可选扩展、拼写检查、空白修剪、单词完成等。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Розумні функції: автовідступ, поведінка розумного копіювання/вирізання, показ пробілів вибраного тексту та в кінці рядків прямо з коробки та додаткові розширення для роботи з Markdown, перевірки правопису, обтинання пробілів, автозавершення слів та багато іншого.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Baştan sona akıllı özellikler: otomatik girinti, akıllı kesme/kopyalama davranışı, varsayılan olarak seçilen metin için ve satırların sonundaki boşlukları gösterir, isteğe bağlı olarak Markdown eylemleri, yazım denetimi, boşluk düzeltme, sözcük tamamlama ve daha fazlası için uzantılar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Inteligentné funkcie skrz na skrz: automatické odsadzovanie, inteligentné správanie vystrihovania/kopírovania, prepínanie viditeľnosti prázdnych znakov pre označený text a na konci riadkov a voliteľné rozšírenia pre Markdown akcie, kontrolu preklepov, orezávanie prázdnych znakov, dokončovanie slov a viac.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Умные функции: автоматический отступ, умное вырезание/копирование, отображение пробелов выбранного текста и в конце строк по умолчанию, а также дополнительные расширения для работы с Markdown, проверка орфографии, обрезка пробельных символов, завершения слов и многое другое.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Inteligentne funkcje wszędzie tam gdzie to możliwe: automatyczne wcięcia, inteligentne zachowanie przy wycinaniu/kopiowaniu, widoczne białe znaki dla zaznaczonego tekstu oraz na końcach linii domyślnie oraz opcjonalne rozszerzenia dla akcji Markdown, sprawdzanie pisowni, przycinanie białych znaków, dokańczanie słów i więcej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">便利な機能がこんなにも。自動インデント、“便利な行の切り取り／コピー”機能、デフォルトで選択中のテキストと行末の空白を表示する機能、オプションで Markdown アクション・スペルチェック・余分な空白の削除・単語補完などの機能も。</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">יכולות חכמות מעל ומעבר: הזחה אוטומטית, התנהות חכמה לגזירה/העתקה, רווח גלוי לטקסט נבחר ובסופי שורות כבררת מחדל והרחבה כרשות לפעולות Markdown, בדיקת איות, קיצוץ רווחים, השלמת מילים ועוד.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">De nombreuses fonctionnalités intelligentes : indentation automatique, comportement intelligent en matière de couper/copier, espaces blancs visibles pour le texte sélectionné et à la fin des lignes par défaut, et extensions disponibles en option pour les actions Markdown, la vérification orthographique, le découpage des espaces blancs, l'auto-complétion, et plus encore.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones inteligentes en todas partes: sangría automática, comportamiento inteligente de cortar/copiar, espacios en blanco visibles para el texto seleccionado y al final de las líneas de forma predeterminada, y extensiones opcionales para acciones de Markdown, revisión ortográfica, recorte de espacios en blanco, finalización de palabras y más.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Smart features throughout: automatic indentation, smart cut/copy behavior, visible whitespace for selected text and at the end of lines by default, and optional extensions for Markdown actions, spell checking, whitespace trimming, word completion, and more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Smarte Funktionen durch und durch: Automatisches Einrücken, smartes Ausschneiden/Kopieren, standardmäßig sichtbare Leerstellen für markierten Text und am Ende von Zeilen und optionale Erweiterungen für Markdown-Aktionen, Rechtschreibprüfung, Leerstellen-Trimmen, Wortkomplettierungen und vieles mehr.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Přehlídka chytrých funkcí: automatické odsazování, inteligentní chování vyjmutí/zkopírování, ve výchozím stavu viditelné prázdné znaky (whitespace) pro označený text a na konci řádku a volitelná rozšíření pro akce ohledně Markdown, kontrola překlepů, ořezávání prázdných znaků, dokončování slov a další.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">تایبەتمەندیە زیرەکەکان: بۆشایی خۆکاری سەرەتای دێڕ، ڕەفتاری زیرەکی بڕین/لەبەرگرتنەوە، بۆشایی سپی بینراو بۆ دەقی هەڵبژێردراو و لە کۆتایی هێڵەکان بە شێوەی سەرەکی، و پێوەکراوی ئارەزوومەندانە بۆ کردارەکانی مارکداون، هەڵەچنی، کورتکردنەوەی بۆشایی سپی، تەواوکردنی ووشەکان، و زیاتر.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Funcions intel·ligents: sagnat automàtic, comportament de retall / còpia intel·ligent, espai en blanc visible per al text seleccionat i al final de les línies de manera predeterminada, i extensions opcionals per a accions del Markdown, correcció ortogràfica, retall d’espais en blanc, acabament de paraules i molt més.</p>
    <p>Adapt Code to your workflow: you can tweak the behavior and interface as needed with a handful of useful and well-considered extensions and preferences.</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">使 Code 适应您的工作流程：您可以根据需要使用一些有用且经过深思熟虑的扩展和首选项来调整行为和界面。</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Пристосуйте код до свого робочого процесу: за необхідності можна налаштувати поведінку та інтерфейс за допомогою кількох корисних та добре продуманих розширень та налаштувань.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kod uygulamasını iş akışınıza uyarlayın: Bir avuç kullanışlı ve iyi düşünülmüş uzantı ve tercihle davranışı ve arayüzü gerektiği gibi değiştirebilirsiniz.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Upravte si Kód podľa štýlu vašej práce: môžete si upraviť správanie a vzhľad rozhrania podľa potreby pomocou množstva užitočných a premyslených rozšírení a predvolieb.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Приспособте Код к своему рабочему процессу: при необходимости можно настроить поведение и интерфейс с помощью нескольких полезных и хорошо продуманных расширений и настроек.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Przystosuj Kod do twojego stylu pracy: możesz dostosować zachowania oraz interfejs do twoich potrzeb przy użyciu kilku użytecznych oraz przemyślanych wtyczek i ustawień.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">“コード”を自身のワークフローに導入しましょう。厳選された便利な拡張機能と設定を使って、挙動とインターフェースを必要に応じて調整できます。</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">התאמת קוד לתהליך העבודה שלך: אפשר לשפצר את ההתנהגות והמנשקים כראות עיניך עם מגוון הרחבות והעדפות שימושיות וראויות.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Adaptez Code à votre flux de travail : vous pouvez modifier le comportement et l'interface selon vos besoins grâce à une poignée d'extensions et de préférences utiles et bien pensées.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Adapte Code a su flujo de trabajo: puede modificar el comportamiento y la interfaz según sea necesario con un puñado de extensiones y preferencias útiles y bien consideradas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">Adapt Code to your workflow: you can tweak the behaviour and interface as needed with a handful of useful and well-considered extensions and preferences.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Passen Sie Code an Ihren Workflow an: Sie können das Verhalten und die Oberfläche mit einer Handvoll nützlichen und speziell designten Erweiterungen ganz nach Ihren Bedürfnissen anpassen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Upravte si Code podle stylu své práce: je možné vyladit chování rozhraní dle potřeby pomocí mnoha užitečných a promyšlených rozšíření a předvoleb.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">کۆد بۆ ژینگەی کارەکەت بگونجێنە: دەتوانیت بە ئارەزووی خۆت دەستکاری ڕەفتار و ڕووکاری کۆد بکەیت لە ڕێکخستنەکان و زیادکراوە سوودبەخشەکان.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Adapteu el Codi al vostre flux de treball: podeu modificar-ne el comportament i la interfície segons sigui necessari amb un grapat d’extensions i preferències útils i ben considerades.</p>
    <p>There's a ton more:</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh_CN">更多:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">А також:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bir ton daha özellik var:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">A je toho omnoho viac:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">И еще много чего:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">To wciąż nie wszystko:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ja">そのほかの機能:</p>
    <p xml:lang="he">ויש עוד המון:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Et bien plus encore :</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Hay mucho más:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en_GB">There's a ton more:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Und es gibt noch eine Menge mehr:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">A je toho mnohem více:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ckb">یەک تەن تایبەتمەندی تر ماوە:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Hi ha moltes més coses:</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Solarized Light, Solarized Dark, and High Contrast color schemes that affect the whole UI</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">影响整个 UI 的 Solarized Light、Solarized Dark 和 High Contrast 配色方案</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Solarized світла, Solarized темна, а також висококонтрастна кольорові схеми, які впливають на весь інтерфейс</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tüm kullanıcı arayüzünü etkileyen Açık Renk Tema, Koyu Renk Tema ve Yüksek karşıtlık renk şemaları</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Schémy farieb Solarizovaná svetlá, Solarizovaná tmavá a Vysoký kontrast, ktoré sa týkajú celého používateľského rozhrania</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Цветовые схемы Solarized Light, Solarized Dark и High Contrast, которые влияют на весь интерфейс</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Motywy słoneczny jasny, słoneczny ciemny oraz wysoki kontrast wpływające na cały interfejs</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">UI 全体に反映される、Solarized Light、Solarized Dark、ハイコントラストカラースキーム</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">זריחה בהירה, זריחה כהה וערכות צבע עם ניגודיות גבוהה שמשפיעות על כל מנשק המשתמש</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Thèmes de couleurs Solarized Light, Solarized Dark et Contraste élevé qui affectent l'ensemble de l'interface utilisateur</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Esquemas de color Solarized Light, Solarized Dark y Alto Contraste que afectan a toda la interfaz de usuario</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Solarised Light, Solarised Dark, and High Contrast colour schemes that affect the whole UI</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Solarized Light, Solarized Dark und High Contrast Farbschemata, die die komplette Oberfläche beeinflussen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Schémata barev Solarized Light, Solarized Dark, a Vysoký kontrast, která se týkají celého uživatelského rozhraní</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">ڕووکاری ڕەنگ هەتاوی، و تاریک و سکیمەکانی ڕەنگی کۆنتراست بەرز کە تەواوی دیزاینی ئەپەکە دەگرێتەوە</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Esquemes de colors Solarized Light, Solarized Dark i High Contrast que afecten tota la interfície d’usuari</li>
      <li>Togglable sidebar to fit your workflow</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可切换的侧边栏以适合您的工作流程</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Перемикання бічної панелі для зручності роботи</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İş akışınıza uyacak şekilde değiştirilebilir kenar çubuğu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Voliteľný bočný panel, ktorý zapadá do vášho spôsobu práce</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Динамичная панель сбоку подходящая вам</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przełączalny panel boczny by pracować tak jak chesz</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">ワークフローに応じて表示・非表示が可能なサイドバー</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">לוח צד גמיש שמתאים לאופן העבודה שלך</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Barre latérale amovible pour s'adapter à votre flux de travail</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Barra lateral conmutable para adaptarse a tu flujo de trabajo</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Togglable sidebar to fit your workflow</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">An- und ausschaltbare Seitenleiste um Ihrem Workflow zu entsprechen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Volitelný postranní panel, který zapadá do vašeho způsobu práce</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">سایدباڕێک کە دەتوانیت بیشاریتەوە یان وەکو خۆی بیهێڵییەوە، واتا ڕەوتکراوە</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Barra lateral commutable per adaptar-se al flux de treball</li>
      <li>Smart indentation and .editorconfig support</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">智能缩进和 .editorconfig 支持</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Розумні автовідступи та підтримка .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Akıllı girintili yazma ve .editorconfig desteği</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Inteligentné odsadzovanie a podpora štandardu .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Умный отступ и поддержка .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Inteligentne wcięcia i wsparcie dla .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">便利なインデント機能と .editorconfig への対応</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">הזחה חכמה ותמיכה ב־‎.editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Indentation intelligente et prise en charge des fichiers .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Compatibilidad con sangría inteligente y .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Smart indentation and .editorconfig support</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Smartes Einrücken und .editorconfig Unterstützung</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Chytré odsazování a podpora standardu .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">دانانی بۆشایی سەرەتای دێڕ بە شێوەیەکی زیرەکانە و پاڵپشتی کردنی .editorconfig</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Sagnat intel·ligent i suport per a .editorconfig</li>
      <li>Browser-class tabs with drag-and-drop, duplication, undo closing, and tab history</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">具有拖放、复制、撤消关闭和选项卡历史记录的浏览器类选项卡</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вкладки, як у переглядачі з перетягуванням, дублюванням, скасуванням закриття й історією вкладки</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Sürükle ve bırak, çoğaltma, kapatmayı geri alma ve sekme geçmişine sahip tarayıcı sınıfı sekmeler</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Karty ako vo webovom prehliadači, ktoré je možné presúvať, duplikovať, znova zobraziť po zatvorení a prezrieť si ich históriu</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Вкладки браузерного качества с возможностью перетаскивания в другое окно, дублированием, отменой закрытия и историей вкладок</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Karty w stylu przeglądarek z przeciąganiem, duplikacją, cofnięciem zamknięcia oraz historią kart</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">ドラッグアンドドロップ、タブの複製、閉じたタブの復元、タブ履歴など、ブラウザー並みの機能を持つタブ</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">לשוניות ברמת דפדפן עם גרירה ושחרור, שכפול, ביטול סגירה והיסטוריית לשוניות</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Onglets comme dans un navigateur, avec glisser-déposer, duplication, annulation de la fermeture et historique des onglets</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Pestañas tipo navegador con función de arrastrar y soltar, duplicar, deshacer cierre e historial de pestañas</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Browser-class tabs with drag-and-drop, duplication, undo closing, and tab history</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Browserartiges Tabverhalten mit Drag &amp; Drop, Duplizieren, Schließen-rückgängig-Funktion und Tab-Verlaufsfunktion</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Panely jako ve webovém prohlížeči, které je možné přesouvat, duplikovat, brát zpět zavření a také jejich historie</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">تابەکان لەناو ئەم ئەپەدا، وەکو تابەکانی وێبگەڕ (بڕاوزەر) وایە، دەتوانیت ڕاکێشان بە تابەکان بکەیت یان بە دوویان بکەیت. هەر وەکو وێبگەڕ، دەتوانیت تابێكی داخراو دوبارە بگەڕێنییە یان سەیری مێژووی تابە کراوەکانت بکەیت</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Pestanyes de la classe del navegador amb arrossegar i deixar anar, duplicació, desfer el tancament i historial de pestanyes</li>
      <li>Display the current line and character—and quickly jump to a new line</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">显示当前行和字符——并快速跳转到新行</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Знайдіть поточний рядок чи символ і швидко перейдіть до нового рядка</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Geçerli satırı ve karakteri görüntüleyin ve hızla yeni bir satıra geçin</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zobrazte si aktuálny riadok a znak – a rýchlo preskočte na nový riadok</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Отображает текущую строку и символ — и быстро переходит к новой строке</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyświetl aktualną linię oraz znak oraz szybko przejdź do nowej linii</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">現在カーソルのある行と列を表示します。そして、別の行に瞬時に移動できます</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">הצגת השורה והתו הנוכחיים לצד האפשרות לקפוץ לשורה חדשה</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Affichage de la ligne et du caractère courants, et saut rapide à une nouvelle ligne</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Muestra la línea y el carácter actuales y salta rápidamente a una nueva línea</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Display the current line and character—and quickly jump to a new line</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Anzeigen der aktuellen Zeile und Zeichen — und schnelles Springen zu einer neuen Zeile</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Zobrazit stávající řádek jako znak – a rychle skočit na nový řádek</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">پشاندانی کارێکتەر و دێڕی ئێستا و بەخێرای بازدان بۆ دێڕی تازە</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Es mostra la línia i el caràcter actuals i se salta ràpidament a una línia nova.</li>
      <li>Scroll past the end of the file so you can keep the current line where it's comfortable</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">滚动到文件的末尾，以便您可以将当前行保持在舒适的位置</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Прокрутіть у кінець файлу, щоб зберегти поточний рядок там, де зручно</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Dosyanın son satırını istediğiniz yere kaydırın, böylece geçerli satırı rahat olduğu yerde tutabilirsiniz</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Posúvajte sa až za koniec súboru, takže môžete ponechať aktuálny riadok v takej výške, v akej je to pohodlné</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Прокрутите файл до конца, чтобы сохранить текущую строку там, где это удобно</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przejdź do końca pliku by przechować aktualną linię tam gdzie jest wygodnie</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">ファイルの最終行より先にもスクロールできるので、編集中の行をお好きな位置に表示できます</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">גלילה מעבר לסוף הקובץ כדי לשמור על השורה הנוכחית במקום נוח</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Faites défiler le fichier jusqu'à la fin pour garder la ligne en cours là où c'est confortable</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Desplácese más allá del final del archivo para que pueda mantener la línea actual donde le resulte más cómodo</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Scroll past the end of the file so you can keep the current line where it's comfortable</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Über das Ende der Datei hinaus scrollen, um die aktuelle Zeile dort zu sehen, wo es bequem ist</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Posunování za konec souboru, takže je možné ponechat stávající řádek tam, kde je to pohodlné</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">سکرۆڵکردن لە کۆتایی فایلەکە بۆ ئەوەی بتوانیت هێڵی ئێستا لەو شوێنەی کە ئاسوودەیە بهێڵیتەوە</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Desplaceu-vos fins al final del fitxer per mantenir la línia actual on sigui còmode.</li>
      <li>Optional mini-map to make navigating large files easier</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh_CN">可选的缩略图，使浏览大文件更容易</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Опційна міні-карта для полегшення навігації у великих файлах</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Büyük dosyalarda gezinmeyi kolaylaştırmak için isteğe bağlı mini harita</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Voliteľná minimapa, ktorá zjednodušuje pohyb po väčších súboroch</li>
      <li xml:lang="ru">Мини-карта для упрощения навигации по большим файлам</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Opcjonalna mini-mapa by łatwiej nawigować w dużych plikach</li>
      <li xml:lang="ja">行数の多いファイルでも移動が簡単になるミニマップ機能もオプションで用意</li>
      <li xml:lang="he">מפה ממוזערת כרשות כדי להקל על הניווט בקבצים גדולים</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Mini-carte en option pour faciliter la navigation dans les gros fichiers</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Minimapa opcional para facilitar la navegación en archivos grandes</li>
      <li xml:lang="en_GB">Optional mini-map to make navigating large files easier</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Optionale Mini-Map um das Navigieren in großen Dateien zu vereinfachen</li>
      <li xml:lang="cs">Volitelná minimapa, která usnadňuje pohyb po větších souborech</li>
      <li xml:lang="ckb">نەخشۆچکەیەکی ئارەزوومەندانە بۆ ئاسانکردنی هاتووچۆکردن بەناو فایلە گەورەکان</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Minimapa opcional per facilitar la navegació per fitxers grans</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <releases>
    <release version="6.2.0" date="2022-04-01" urgency="medium">
      <description>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>The current document filename is now shown as the window title in multitasking view</li>
          <li>Hidden folders are now shown in the project sidebar</li>
          <li>The currently selected result and the number of results is displayed while searching</li>
          <li>The search bar now has a regular expression mode</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>It is now possible to change Git branch with untracked files present in a project</li>
          <li>Crashes are prevented while searching in large projects</li>
          <li>The correct document is now focused after opening Code from an external program</li>
          <li>Line duplication is now actioned correctly if there is no selection present</li>
          <li>Code no longer crashes when asked to open an unknown URI format</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.1.0" date="2021-11-23" urgency="medium">
      <description>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Projects with the same name now include their parent folder name as well</li>
          <li>When scrolling to search results, overshoot slightly for better visibility</li>
          <li>Use the FileChooser portal instead of the one from GTK</li>
          <li>Center the global search dialog over the main Code window</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix visibility of Terminal button on Welcome page</li>
          <li>Fix some keyboard shortcuts affecting unfocused Document instead of focused Terminal</li>
          <li>Close Terminal if shell exited and create new Terminal if re-opened with no shell</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>"Visible whitespace" combobox is now a switch</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.0.1" date="2021-08-28" urgency="medium">
      <description>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix crash when creating new window from tab drop</li>
          <li>Ensure files created from the sidebar are automatically opened</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Improvements:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Hide project chooser button when hiding sidebar</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Ensure all copy is translatable</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="6.0.0" date="2021-07-15" urgency="medium">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New Markdown plugin for WYSIWYG-like editing.</li>
          <li>Switch Git branches or create new ones in project folder context menus</li>
          <li>Show Git diff status in source view gutters</li>
          <li>Full text search within project folder.</li>
          <li>Save and restore cursor position between sessions</li>
          <li>Close files from a project when that project is closed</li>
          <li>Show full file path in tab tooltips</li>
          <li>Clear lines with Ctrl + K</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Allow Spell Checker extension in Markdown files</li>
          <li>Improve multi-line duplication</li>
          <li>Remember whether the sidebar is open</li>
          <li>Set window title to the focused file</li>
          <li>Add keyboard shortcuts for next and previous documents</li>
          <li>Show full document path in tab tooltip</li>
          <li>Update Pastebin plugin</li>
          <li>Correctly indent last line when using the preserve whitespace plugin</li>
          <li>Keep syntax highlighting when duplicating a file</li>
          <li>Expand a collapsed folder if you attempt to open it twice</li>
          <li>Fix an issue where searches are lost when Code loses focus</li>
          <li>Start Vim plugin in command mode</li>
          <li>Fix and add new Vim commands</li>
          <li>Show project folders with a hidden root folder</li>
          <li>Allow launching with pkexec and disallow launching with sudo</li>
          <li>Remove split view</li>
          <li>Remove browser preview</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.4.1" date="2020-06-09">
      <description>
        <p>Fixes:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix empty sidebar layout, ensuring folders can always be added</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Minor updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Scroll past the end of a file</li>
          <li>More efficiently save and restore window position</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.4.0" date="2020-04-01">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Include Git status in file tooltips</li>
          <li>Option for explicit case-sensitive Find</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Correctly show Toggle Comment menu item when no text is selected</li>
          <li>Fixed font switch alignment</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.3.0" date="2020-02-29">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>New "Close Other Folders" menu item to help clean up your sidebar</li>
          <li>Save and restore cyclic search setting</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Add keyboard shortcuts to menu items</li>
          <li>Make sidebar folder items not selectable</li>
          <li>Center new windows</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.2.0" date="2020-01-09">
      <description>
        <p>New features:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Visually deprioritize .gitignored files in project sidebar</li>
          <li>Smart cut/copy lines with no active selection</li>
          <li>Add a confirmation dialog to the "Restore" action</li>
          <li>Add "Open In" menu to the top-level folder in the folder manager</li>
          <li>Don't show temporary files in the folder manager</li>
          <li>Add brackets completion and auto-indent by default</li>
          <li>Zoom terminal plugin with keyboard</li>
          <li>Honor global privacy setting when saving and restoring</li>
        </ul>
        <p>Other updates:</p>
        <ul>
          <li>Simplify "Draw spaces" preference</li>
          <li>Fix the keyboard shortcut for going backwards in search results</li>
          <li>Fix opening files from relative paths in Terminal</li>
          <li>Fix null file dialog when opening a new window via the dock</li>
          <li>Add "=" as a zoom key</li>
          <li>Change search entry icon when results aren't found</li>
          <li>Enter name of new file before creating it</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.1" date="2019-03-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Use Granite.MessageDialog throughout</li>
          <li>Include non-text files in sidebar</li>
          <li>Fix Remove Current View</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.1.0" date="2019-03-06">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Fix New Window desktop action behavior</li>
          <li>Properly synchronize Ctrl+N key presses with number of new documents spawned</li>
          <li>Build system fix for editorconfig dependency</li>
          <li>Add Change Branch context menu item</li>
          <li>Avoid possible startup crash related to how plugins load</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0.2" date="2019-01-03">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Smarter file saving behavior</li>
          <li>File saving fixes</li>
          <li>Don't add temporary files to tab restore</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0.1" date="2018-11-30">
      <description>
        <ul>
          <li>Don't recreate deleted files when restoring session</li>
          <li>Restore line wrap preference</li>
          <li>Add accel tooltips</li>
          <li>Minor bug fixes</li>
          <li>Updated translations</li>
        </ul>
      </description>
    </release>
    <release version="3.0" date="2018-10-16"/>
    <release version="2.4.1" date="2017-02-20"/>
  </releases>
  <provides>
    <binary>io.elementary.code</binary>
  </provides>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1">
    <content_attribute id="violence-cartoon">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-fantasy">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-realistic">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-bloodshed">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-sexual">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-desecration">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-slavery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="violence-worship">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-alcohol">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-narcotics">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="drugs-tobacco">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-nudity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-themes">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-homosexuality">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-prostitution">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-adultery">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="sex-appearance">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-profanity">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-humor">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="language-discrimination">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-chat">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-info">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-audio">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-location">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="social-contacts">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-purchasing">none</content_attribute>
    <content_attribute id="money-gambling">none</content_attribute>
  </content_rating>
  <developer_name>elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="zh_CN">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt_BR">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ja">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="hu">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="he">elementary בע״מ.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en_GB">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ckb">کۆمپانیای ئێلەمێنتەری هاوپشک.</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">elementary, Inc.</developer_name>
  <url type="homepage">https://elementary.io/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/elementary/code/issues</url>
  <url type="donation">https://elementary.io/get-involved#funding</url>
  <url type="help">https://github.com/elementary/code/discussions/categories/q-a</url>
  <url type="translate">https://l10n.elementary.io/projects/code</url>
  <update_contact>contact_AT_elementary.io</update_contact>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elementary/code/master/data/screenshot.png</image>
    </screenshot>
    <screenshot>
      <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/elementary/code/master/data/screenshot-dark.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
